Guide to the William L. Mertz transportation collection, 1955-1990
George Mason University Libraries
- William L. Mertz transportation collection
  - Highway Development: How was Our Modern Road System Created? - Notebook 11 Fall 1929 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Freedom of the Road - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 11/12 -15/28 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Effect of Six Wheel Vehicles on Highway Design - Notebook 11 10/18/28 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Federal Aid as a Road building Policy: What is it and What has it Accomplished? 4/28 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Federal Aid Helps Close Highway Gaps - Notebook 11[Portland Evening News] 1/28/28 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Highways in the Making - Notebook 11 [6th Annual Paving Conference] 11/28 - 12/2/27 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Highway Policies - Notebook 11 [AASHO meeting: MacDonald threatened to withhold funds from jurisdictions not completing Intercontinental routes.] 10/3-10/6/27 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - The Bureau of Public Roads - Notebook 11 [description of organization structure] 1/27 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - The Aims and Intentions of the Bureau of Public Roads - Notebook 11 January 1927 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Highway Finance - Federal, State and Local - Notebook 11 [American Road Builders' Assn.] 1/11-1/15/26 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Two Thousand Years of Road Building - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 11/8-12/26 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - The Highways as an Interstate Problem - Notebook 11 10/26 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - The History and Development of Road Building in the United States - Notebook 11 10/6/26 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Federal Government's Part in th Country's Highway Program - Notebook 11 4/29/20 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Federal Aid for Highway Improvement - Notebook 11 3/29/20 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Address Before Road Builders' Assoc - Notebook 11 2/13/20 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Comprehensive Survey of Highway Situation in the United States - Notebook 11 1/29/20 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - The Present System of Federal Control and Aid for Highways, Its Results, Merits and Limitations - Notebook 11 12/8/19 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Road Construction and Maintenance and the Use of Highways from the national Standpoint - Notebook 11 3/23/23 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - What Our Highways Mean to Us - Notebook 11 [Trade Winds] 2/23 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Uncle Sam's Interest in State Highways - Notebook 11 Annual Convention of Good Roads Assoc 1/29-31/23 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - The Engineer as a Leader in Public Service - Notebook 11 6/21/23 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - The Functioning of Federal Aid in the Development of Highway Transportation - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 12/6/22 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Highway Achievements and Prospects - Notebook 11 [Highway Green Book] 1922 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Road Building Progress - Notebook 11 11/22/23 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Annual Meeting of U.S. Chamber of Commerce - Notebook 11 5/16/22 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Status and Relative Progress of the Federal-Aid Highway Program - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 10/11/49 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Engineering in Highway Administration - Notebook 11 9/26/49 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Some Immediately Important Problems in Highway Development - Notebook 11 3/10/49 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Time Element of the Road-Building Program - Notebook 11 3/2/49 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Past, Present and Future of Our State Highway Systems - Notebook 11 3/1/49 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Highway Safety [Driver Behavior] - Notebook 11 11/16/48 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Improved Methods of Transport and Their Significance - Notebook 11 1/48 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Review of the Post-war Highway program - Notebook 11 1/27/48 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Highway Policy Questions - Notebook 11 3/3/48 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - The Progress of the national Highway Program - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 9/22/47 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Address: Business Men's Conference on Urban Problems - Notebook 11 [highway program and its relation to cities] 9/11-12/47 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - The Case for Urban Expressways - Notebook 11 [American City Magazine] 6/47 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Toll Roads - Notebook 11 [Response to the New Hampshire Sunday News] 4/22/47 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Highway Planning for Community Service - Notebook 11 2/25/47 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Interstate or Super Highways - Notebook 11 1/24/47 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - The Highway Construction Program - Notebook 11 1/22/47 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - The Highway Improvement Program In relation to the Conventional Public Works Concept - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 12/20/46 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - A National Program for Secondary Road Development - Notebook 11 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - A New Pattern for National Highway Development - Notebook 11 5/20/46 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Highway Development Under the New Legislation - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 1/30/46 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - County Highways and the New Federal Highway Legislation - Notebook 11 6/18/45 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Analyzing Transportation Needs of Urban areas - A New Technique: Federal Aid From the National Viewpoints: Housing Development and Express Highways - Notebook 11 11/3/44 to 1/11/45 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Preparation for the Postwar Highway Program - Notebook 11 2/7/44 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Preparing for the Postwar Highway Program - Notebook 11 2/7/44 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Proposed Interregional Highway System As It Affects Cities - Notebook 11 American Society of Civil Engineers 1/21/44 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Future Highway Program - Notebook 11 [AASHO] 12/2/43 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Transcript of Informal Remarks of Thomas H MacDonald before the Annual Meeting of Association to Highway Officials of North Atlantic States - Notebook 11 [approval procedures for highway projects] 2/18/43 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - War's Challenge to Highway Administrators - Notebook 11 12/7/42 (Box 11)
  - The Essential Relationship of Highway Transport to the National Security - Notebook 11 2/26/42 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - The Indispensable Quality of Highways to the National Defense - Notebook 11 9/29/41 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Highways for National Defense The Indispensable Quality of Highways to the National Defense - Notebook 11 July 1941 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - The New Federal Highway System The Indispensable Quality of Highways to the National Defense - Notebook 11 5/31/41 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Highways and the National Defense The Indispensable Quality of Highways to the National Defense - Notebook 11 [reflections regarding Germany's Autobahn] 9/16/40 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Accord of Discord [amongst different interest groups] The Indispensable Quality of Highways to the National Defense - Notebook 11 1/29/40 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - The American Automobile Association - Notebook 11 [planning surveys] 11/17/39 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Highway Program for the United States - Notebook 11 11/13/39 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - national Road Building Through State - Federal Cooperation - Notebook 11 10/10/39 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Contrasting United States and European Practices in Road Development - Notebook 11 12/5/38 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - The Michigan Good Roads Association - Notebook 11[anti diversion section of 1934 Act] 10/20/38 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Modern Roads for Modern Needs - Notebook 11 11/18/38 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - article for the Annual Automobile Show Issue of the new York Times - Notebook 11 [urban needs] 10/1/38 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - An Action Program to Advance Safety on the Highways - Notebook 11 1/17/38 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - What is Expected of Our Highways - Notebook 11 9/27/37 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Motor Transportation - A Forward View - Notebook 11 7/21/37 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Highways of The Future - Notebook 11 5/6/37 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Eighteenth Annual Convention of the Associated General Contractors of America - Notebook 11 [National Recovery Act 2/15/37 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Relating Highway Planning to the Traffic Requirements - Notebook 11 1/12/37 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - The Changing Highway Picture - Notebook 11 1/11/37 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Looking Toward the Highway Future - Notebook 11 [Autobahn] 12/7/36 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Future of Our Highways [How will additional Mileage be built and old construction maintained - Notebook 11 10/19/36 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Remarks to the AAA - Notebook 11 11/20/36 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Highway Improvement Policies - Federal, State and Local: Improvement of Secondary Roads - Notebook 11 4/27/36 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Highway Progress Responsibility - Notebook 11 2/12/36 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - A Review of Highway Progress - Notebook 11 [1929-1935 1/20/36 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Progress in Public Works Highway Construction - Notebook 11 [ summary of 3 speeches on related topics] 9/30/35, 10/10/38, and 11/5/35 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Results from the Public Works Highway Program - Notebook 11 4/27/35 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Memorandum on National Highway Programs [To the Contracting Industry] - Notebook 11 9/11/35 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Future Development of the Art and Science of Highway Engineering - Notebook 11 9/5/52 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Critical Aspects of the Current Highway Program - Notebook 11 10/23/51 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Relation of the Highway Program to the National Economy - Notebook 11 12/4/50 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - A review of Our Highway Policies - Notebook 11 10/5/50 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Activities in Furtherance of International Affairs - Notebook 11 10/1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Interstate System in Urban Areas 5/16/50 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Acute Problem of Safety on Our Streets and Highways - Notebook 11 6/21/50 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - A New Look At the Federal Aid Program - Notebook 11 3/6/50 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Progress on New Federal Aid Legislation - Notebook 11 4/1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 26th Annual Convention of Association of Highway Officials of North Atlantic States - Notebook 11 2/21/50 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Fifty Years of Accomplishments on State Highways - Notebook 11 [published by Council of State Govt] 5/1950 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Inadequacies of Our Present Highway Transportation Facilities - Notebook 11 11/8/49 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The national System of Interstate Highways - Notebook 11 11/3/49 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - The Bragdon Committee - Note book 13 [monograph of the history of Interstate System] 7/16/1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Bragdon Committee - Notebook 13 [miscellaneous papers] 10/59 - 4/8/60 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bragdon Committee - Notebook 13 [miscellaneous papers] 10/59 - 11/59 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bragdon Committee - Notebook 13 [miscellaneous papers] 11/59 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Bragdon Committee - Notebook 13 [miscellaneous papers] 1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Thomas H. Mac Donald's HRB Papers - Notebook 11 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - MacDonald's Reports to the Department of Highway Finance, HRB - Notebook 11 1935 - 1940 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Choice of Guides - Notebook 11 12/10/52 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Amendments of 1974, January 4, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1973; August 13, 1973 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1970; December 31, 1970 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1968; August 23, 1968 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - An Act to amend section 103 of Title 23, U.S. Code, to amend modifications or revisions in the Interstate System or " The Howard-Cramer Act" January 2, 1968 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Department of Transportation Act; October 15,1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1966; September 13, 1966 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - An Act to provide scenic development and road beautification of the Federal-Aid highway system, or the Highway Beautification Act of 1965; October 22, 1965 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - A Joint resolution to amend the Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1956 to increase the amount authorized for the Interstate System for 1967 and authorize its apportionment; August 28, 1965 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1964; August 13, 1964 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1962; October 23, 1962 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Amendments Act of 1963 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - An Act to amend Title 23, United States Code, relating to the organization of the Bureau of Public Roads; October 4, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1961; June 29, 1961 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1961; July 14,1960 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1959; September 21, 1959 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Tile I - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1956 and Title II - Highway Revenue Act of 1956; June 29,1956 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1958; April 16, 1958 - Notebook - 16 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - An Act to review, codify, and enact into law, title 23 of the U.S. Code, entitled "Highways"; August 27, 1958 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1954; May 6, 1954 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Post Office Appropriations Act of 1922; June 19, 1922 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1952; June 25, 1952 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1950; September 7, 1950 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1948; June 29, 1948 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - An Act to amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act - 1946 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Urban Freeways and Interstate System; March 1976 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - National Transportation Policy;September 1949 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - An Act to amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act and to Authorize Appropriations for Postwar construction of highways and bridges; December 20, 1944 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - An Act to amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act; July 13, 1943 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - An Act to provide cooperation with Central American republics in the construction of the Inter-American Highway; December 26, 1941 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - An Act to supplement the 1916 Road Act and to authorize appropriations for roads urgently needed for the national defense - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - National Highway Study Hearings - Notebook 16 April, May, June, July 1953 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1940 [September 5, 1940] - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1938 - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - An Act to amend the Federal Aid Road Act of 1916[ June 16, 1936] - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - An Act to increase employment by authorizing an appropriation to provide for emergency construction of public highways.. .and amend the Federal Aid Road Act of 1916 -- Hayden Cart wright Act - Notebook 16 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - An Act making supplemental appropriations to provided for Emergency Construction on certain public works... with a view to increasing employment - Notebook 16 12/20/1930 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - An act to Amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act - Notebook 16 5/5/30 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - An Act to Permit the granting of Federal Aid in respect of certain roads and bridges - Notebook 16 3/3/27 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - An Act to amend " An Act to provide that the United States shall aid the States in the construction of rural post roads... " - Notebook 16 6/22/26 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - An Act to amend " An Act to provide that the United States shall aid the States in the construction of rural post roads... " - Notebook 16 2/12/25 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - hearing on creation of Commissions to study Federal Reorganizations and Federal-State Relations 4/14/53 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - National Highway Study, Extract from Hearings before the Subcommittee on Roads - Notebook 16 7/14/53 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - An Act to amend "The Act entitled An Act to provide that the United States Shall aid the States in the construction of rural Post Roads and for other purposes - Notebook 16 11/9/21 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - An Act to provide that the United States Shall aid the States in the construction of rural Post Roads and for other purposes - Notebook 16 7/11/16 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - TRANS Interim Report Notebook 15 [a draft report on an analysis of transportation resource allocation] 6/1/1971 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - TRANS - Interim Report [continuation of folder 47]- Notebook 15 6/1/71 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - TRANS - Interim Report [continuation of folder 48] Notebook 15 6/1/71 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - An Evaluation of Urban Transportation Planning - Notebook 14 2/19/71 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - An Evaluation of Urban Planning - Notebook 14 [continuation of report in folder 50] 2/19/71 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - An Evaluation of Urban Planning - Notebook 14 [continuation of report in folder 51] 2/19/71 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Revenue Sharing for Transportation, March 18, 1971[Presidential proposal to Congress] - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - An Act to amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act as amended; July 31, 1945 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - An Act to amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act and to Authorize Appropriations for Postwar construction of highways and bridges; December 20, 1944 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - An Act to Amend the 1916 Federal Aid Act as amended; July 13, 1943 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - An Act to provide for cooperation with Central American republics in the construction of the Inter-American Highways; December 26, 1941 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - An Act to supplement the 1916 Road Act and to authorize appropriations for roads urgently needed for the National Defense; November 19, 1941 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - An Act to increase employment by authorizing an appropriation to provide for emergency construction of public highways... and amend the Federal Aid Road Act of 1916, June 18, 1934 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - An Act to amend the 1916 Federal Aid Road Act, as amended - May 5, 1930 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - An Act to amend the Act entitled " An Act to provide that the United States shall aid the States in the construction of rural post roads and for other purposes," approved July 11, 1916; November 9, 1921 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 9a)
  - An Act to amend " An Act to provide that the United States shall aid the States in the construction of rural post roads... ", approved July 11, 1916; February 12, 1925 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 19b)
  - Papers of T. H. MacDonald, 1950 - 1953, vol. 14; n.d. - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Saving the Great Stone Face - 1984 - Notebook 16 [ an abstract of a book] (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Design Standards for the national System of Interstate Highways; August 1, 1945 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Toll Roads and Free Roads; April 27, 1939 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 7079 A bill to provide the location, survey, and building of three transcontinental and six north-south highways H.J. Res. 204 Res 227 (both) A joint resolution creating a superhighways commission; May 18, 1937 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Highway to Prosperity: Super Highway System Can Be Built Without Taxation or Interest; 1939 - Notebook 16 [an abstract from a pamphlet] (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - To Amend the Federal Aid Highway Act of 1916 (Hearing on S. 3309 and H.R. 10140); January 26 and May 13, 1938 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Transcontinental Highway Commission, S.J. Res. 106; April 13, 1937 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Papers of T.H. MacDonald, 1946-1949, Vols. 12 (Partial) and 13; n.d. -- Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Papers of T.H. MacDonald, 1941-1946, Vols. 11 (Partial) and 1(Partial); n.d. -- Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Papers of T.H. MacDonald, 1936-1941, Vols. 9 (Partial), 10 and 11(partial); n.d. -- Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Papers of T.H. MacDonald, 1932-1936, Vols. 8 and 9 (Partial); n.d. -- Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Papers of T.H. MacDonald, 1928-1931, Vols. 6 and 7; n.d. -- Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Papers of T.H. MacDonald, 1923-1927, Vols. 3 (partial), 4, 5; n.d. -- Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - A Study in highway Economics (Harvard Phi Beta Kappa Prize Essay for 1934); 1939 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Report on Joint Board on Interstate Highways, October 30, 1925, November 18, 1925 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Transportation and National Policy; May 1942 [abstract of US National Resources Planning Board report] - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - An analysis of the Federal role in the Planning, Design and Deployment of Roads, Toll Roads and Urban Freeways; May 1983 - Notebook 16 [abstract of dissertation] (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Development of the Interstate Highway Program: 1916 to Date; June 1980 - Notebook 16 [synopsis] (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Interregional Highways, January 12, 1944 - Notebook 16 [book abstract] (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Highways for the National Defense; February 1, 1941 - Notebook 16 [booklet abstract] (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Revenue Sharing for Transportation; March 18, 1971 - Notebook 16 [abstract of presidential message to Congress] (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Surface Transportation Assistance Act of 1978; November 6, 1978 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Consideration for Reimbursement for Certain Highways on the Interstate System; January 7, 1958 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Proposed Formulas for the Reimbursement of the States by the Federal Government for the Cost of Certain Highways on the National System of Interstate and Defense Highways; February 1, 1959 [Report Abstract] -Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - the Zero Milestone souvineer of Dedication, June 4, 1923 [abstract of souvineer booklet] - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Federal Aid Highway Act of 1976; May 5, 1976 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Emergency Highway Energy Conservation Act; January 2, 1974 - Notebook 16 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - National Road: Historic Survey Final Report and Analysis - Notebook 17 6/30/87 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - SimCity: The City Simulator (User Documentation) [Macintosh software]- Notebook 17 1989 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - The 1962 Highway Act: A Study in Artful Interpretation [article from AIP Journal] - Notebook 17 5/69 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - How South Dakota 'stole' an Interstate [reprint of an article from the "Argus Leader"] - Notebook 17 6/28/81 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - The PA Turnpike [copy of article in "American Heritage"] - Notebook 17 May/June 1980 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - National Conference on Highways and Urban Development [article in American Highways] - Notebook 17 10/ 58 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Report Respecting Roads and Canals from the Treasury Department Notebook 17 4/4/1808 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Construction of the Alaska Highway - Notebook 17 1975 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - The Innovation of the Interstate Highway System - Notebook 17 1984 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - "The Road to Happiness" a Highway Motion Picture 4/24 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - To Cross America, early motorists took a long detour [magazine article] - Notebook 17 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence from AASHTO regarding "Yellow Book" - Notebook 17 7/19/90 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - A Man, A Star and amp, A Gun [US Marshals] - notebook 17 6/90 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Lincoln and his Marshall [excerpt "forthcoming" history of the US Marshals - Notebook 17 5/90 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - A Story of Road Signing - Notebook 17 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Handbook of Highway Engineering - Highway Policies and Administration by F. C. Turner (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Federal Highway Act (folder 1 of 2) 4/56-6/56 (Box 15, Folder 2)